xpertravels.com 2015-05-11

# GTI TRAVELS PRIVATE LIMITED - Privacy Policy

|  |  | 

## Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
**Collection of personal information :**  
We may seek your name and email address. Once you book a tour or send a query , you are no longer anonymous to us and you are able to take full advantage of our online offerings. Wherever we collect personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

When you are on our website and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with us alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Please be aware that our advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of those websites linked from and to us. 

**Use of Personal Information :**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, with a customized experience on our website. This includes personalization services, interactive communications and many other services, most of which come absolutely free to you. 

We may, from time to time, send you email regarding its new products and services. In addition, if you indicate upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us, we may occasionally send you direct mails about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only we/our agents (under confidentiality agreements), will send you these direct mailings and only if you do not object to these offers. If you do not wish to receive such mailing, kindly inform us while registering, or at any time by editing your registration information.

Sharing of Information :

As a general rule, we shall will not disclose or share any of your personal information except when we have specifically obtained your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or as permitted in terms of this policy.   
**  
Protection of information :**  
Whenever we handle personal information as described above regardless of where this occurs, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms & conditions and this Privacy Policy. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make best efforts to ensure data security on our systems. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.   
**  
**
